payingadz.com 2015-04-29

# PayingAdz-Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, or mailing address.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1) To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of deliveringthe purchased product or service requested.

2) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site  
feature.

3) To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related  
product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

  **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information maybe provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and Affiliates.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us via our Support page.
